[{"question_text":"\u003cdiv\u003eComputers are not recyclable.\u003c/div\u003e","question_type":"boolean","answers":[{"text":"FALSE","correct":true},{"text":"TRUE","correct":false}],"lesson":"Ethics Lesson"},{"question_text":"\u003cdiv\u003eWhich of the following are examples of copyright infringment?\u003c/div\u003e","question_type":"multiple","answers":[{"text":"Sharing music over the internet","correct":false},{"text":"All of the above","correct":true},{"text":"Copying a CD or DVD and giving a copy to a friend","correct":false},{"text":"Copying information from the internet and pasting it into an essay","correct":false}],"lesson":"Laws lesson"},{"question_text":"A lot of scientific projects run on _____ software.","question_type":"multiple","answers":[{"text":"expensive","correct":false},{"text":"proprietory","correct":false},{"text":"open source","correct":true}]},{"question_text":"Some software programs develop rapidly, gaining new features and adapting to new uses, very often very specialised and experimental. The best software in this case would be:","question_type":"multiple","answers":[{"text":"bespoke","correct":false},{"text":"open source","correct":true},{"text":"proprietory","correct":false}]},{"question_text":"Certain computing projects in education and science are free and maintained by a diverse community of people. Their software is usually distributed as:","question_type":"multiple","answers":[{"text":"off the shelf","correct":false},{"text":"open source","correct":true},{"text":"charity","correct":false}]},{"question_text":"The Data Protection Act pushes companies to take better care of customer data.","question_type":"boolean","answers":[{"text":"TRUE","correct":true},{"text":"FALSE","correct":false}]},{"question_text":"An individual cannot find out what information a company holds about them.","question_type":"boolean","answers":[{"text":"FALSE","correct":true},{"text":"TRUE","correct":false}]},{"question_text":"You can't be prosecuted under the Computer Misuse Act if someone uses an your account and you told them your password.","question_type":"boolean","answers":[{"text":"TRUE","correct":false},{"text":"FALSE","correct":true}]},{"question_text":"The Data Protection Act only applies to individuals.","question_type":"boolean","answers":[{"text":"TRUE","correct":false},{"text":"FALSE","correct":true}]},{"question_text":"The Computer Misuse Act applies to any one using computers anywhere in the world.","question_type":"boolean","answers":[{"text":"TRUE","correct":false},{"text":"FALSE","correct":true}]},{"question_text":"Which of the following is not outlined as a criminal offense in the Computer Misuse act?","question_type":"multiple","answers":[{"text":"Unauthorised modification of computer material","correct":false},{"text":"Unauthorised access to computer material","correct":false},{"text":"Unauthorised access with intent to commit further offences","correct":false},{"text":"Unauthorised lending of computer equipment","correct":true}]},{"question_text":"You can be prosecuted for illegally downloading music from the internet.","question_type":"boolean","answers":[{"text":"FALSE","correct":false},{"text":"TRUE","correct":true}]},{"question_text":"Computer legislation stops people misusing computers.","question_type":"boolean","answers":[{"text":"TRUE","correct":false},{"text":"FALSE","correct":true}]},{"question_text":"Which legislation is not related to computer use?","question_type":"multiple","answers":[{"text":"Design copyright and patents act","correct":false},{"text":"Data protection act","correct":false},{"text":"Computer misuse act","correct":false},{"text":"Parliament act","correct":true}]},{"question_text":"Which of the following materials is not found in a computer?","question_type":"multiple","answers":[{"text":"Mercury","correct":false},{"text":"Uranium","correct":true},{"text":"Lead","correct":false},{"text":"Arsenic","correct":false}]},{"question_text":"As computers become more widespread which of the following will not be an environmental consideration?","question_type":"multiple","answers":[{"text":"Waste","correct":false},{"text":"Deforestation","correct":true},{"text":"Energy consumption","correct":false}]},{"question_text":"Computer crime isn't as important as real-life crime.","question_type":"boolean","answers":[{"text":"FALSE","correct":true},{"text":"TRUE","correct":false}]},{"question_text":"Information posted about yourself on a social networking site is private to you.","question_type":"boolean","answers":[{"text":"FALSE","correct":true},{"text":"TRUE","correct":false}]},{"question_text":"The rise of the internet has increased the number of ethical considerations companies need to follow.","question_type":"boolean","answers":[{"text":"FALSE","correct":false},{"text":"TRUE","correct":true}]},{"question_text":"Ethical standards are written for computing professionals to follow.","question_type":"boolean","answers":[{"text":"TRUE","correct":true},{"text":"FALSE","correct":false}]},{"question_text":"Ethical considerations are legally binding for companies.","question_type":"boolean","answers":[{"text":"TRUE","correct":false},{"text":"FALSE","correct":true}]},{"question_text":"Windows is an example of an open source operating system","question_type":"multiple","answers":[{"text":"True","correct":false},{"text":"False","correct":true}]},{"question_text":"Which of the following statements is false about proprietary software?","question_type":"multiple","answers":[{"text":"A fee is usually required to purchase a software licence","correct":false},{"text":"The software cannot be copied, modified or shared","correct":false},{"text":"An example of the software is the Microsoft Office Suite","correct":false},{"text":"The software can be copied, modified or shared","correct":true}]},{"question_text":"Which of the following statements is true about open source software?","question_type":"multiple","answers":[{"text":"The software is not available for public use","correct":false},{"text":"There is normally a cost to pay for a license to use the software","correct":false},{"text":"The software can be copied, modified or shared","correct":true},{"text":"The software cannot be copied, modified or shared","correct":false}]},{"question_text":"Which legislation governs the act of intellectual property theft?","question_type":"multiple","answers":[{"text":"The Computer Misuse Act","correct":false},{"text":"The Freedom of Information Act","correct":false},{"text":"The Copyright, Designs and Patents Act","correct":true},{"text":"The Data Protection Act","correct":false}]},{"question_text":"Which legislation governs the act of hacking?","question_type":"multiple","answers":[{"text":"The Creative Commons License","correct":false},{"text":"The Freedom of Information Act","correct":false},{"text":"The Computer Misuse Act","correct":true},{"text":"The Data Protection Act","correct":false}]}]